

elsa.pepaj@gmail.com +1 (516) 523-6387

Porfolio: https://elsapepaj.wixsite.com/elsapepaj Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/elsa-pepaj/

Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/architepp/

I am a newly-graduated architect with experience in designing commercial buildings and creating accurate 2D and 3D technical images. I have a knack for working collaboratively and coming up with creative solutions to complex design and sustainability issues. I am skilled at creating clear specifications and communicating with contractors and other key personnel.

Education

• Master of Sciences in Architecture and Urban Design

POLIS UNIVERSITY at Tirana, Albania | October 2017 - July 2022

 Master of Sciences in Architecture and Planning

ANHALT UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES at Dessau, Germany | October 2021 - March 2022

High School Secondary Education
Diploma in General Education III years
28 NENTORI at Shkoder, Albania | September
2014 - June 2017

Key Skills

.

AutoCad 2D/3D

••••

Rhino 2D/3D

••••

Twinmotion rendering

••••

Adobe Photoshop

••••

Adobe Illustrator

••000

Grasshopper

••000

Autodesk Revit

••••

V-Ray

Sketchup

Professional Experience

Junior Architect

MetroPolis Architecture and Planning | April 2022 - September 2022

- Assisted the architectural team with building codes and regulation research.
- Created detailed and accurate technical drawings and performed 3D modeling tasks.
- Assisted with the design of corporate buildings and generated precise measurements and specifications
- Assessed architectural plans for sustainability and environmental impact
- Created 3D images using Rhinoceros and Sketch-Up software

Junior Architect

Kontakt Al Sh.p.k| May 2021 - August 2021

Ass. Architect at Marga Complex

- · Assisted the architectural team with building codes and regulation research
- Worked collaboratively with a multidisciplinary team, including tradespeople, independent contractors, and district representatives
- Visited proposed building sites to take measurements and observe characteristics, reporting findings to the senior architect
- Created detailed and accurate technical drawings and performed 3D modeling tasks
- Drafting of the architectural project.
- Masonry and facade control in the field.
- Drawing up measurement books.
- Aesthetic control (laying tiles) and (installation of windows).

Accomplishments

WINNER OF THE 1ST PRIZE

 "Architectural reconstitution of spaces in the building of the Central state Film archive." - Organized by the Albanian Central State Film Archive with the collaboration of the Polis University.

WINNER OF THE 1ST PRIZE

 "Develop and promote the tourism potential of Apollonia and the Fier country" international competition ViaEgnatia2.0, an online hackathon organized by the Embassy of France in Albania with the collaboration of the French Alliance in Tirana.

Affiliations

HACKATHON

November 2020

ViaEgnatia 2.0 hackathon's objective is to develop virtual tourism around Apollonia and in the Fier country. This hackathon aims to promote innovation and information technologies among the youths and support the best projects. ViaEgnatia 2.0 will be the Albanian event for Novembre Numerique 2020 on the topic related to tourism, digital, and Apollonia during the whole month of November.

WORKSHOP

September 2020 - October 2020

TAW - Tirana Architecture Weeks - held in Tirana

(Open Lectures, workshops, scientific conferences)

PARALEL T "THE LINE", led by Matilde Higuail | Luis Hilti

Is about exploring Tirana, analyzing landscapes, art & walks. Walking on a straight line and mapping while walking and documenting outdoors & indoors. The Line is an arbitrary straight line traced across the globe. http://tiranaarchitectureweek.com/institute-for-linear-research/

WORKSHOP

September 2019 - October 2019

TDW - Tirana Design Weeks - held in Tirana

(Open Lectures, workshops, scientific conferences)

CARTOGRAPHY OF AN ACTION, led by Julio Gotor Valcarel

Is about to claim those intersecting spaces of the city in a new and holistic way, actions that creates a link between the individual and the site. It proposes a way to interact with it, an action that can reveal a lost reality of the site, a way to unveil the forgotten.

In the end, the proposal is a methodology of how to understand the city and its landscape.

http://www.tiranadesignweek.com/home.html

WORKSHOP

September 2018 - October 2018

TAW - Tirana Architecture Weeks - held in Tirana

(Open Lectures, workshops, scientific conferences)

ARTHROPODS / Augumenting Habitation, led by James Stevens

Changing the way of perceiving the surrounding through arthropods. Augmented reality and architecture.

http://futurearchitectureplatform.org/programme/54/tirana-architecture-weeks-cohabitation-tactics/

Volunteer

VOLUNTEER STAFF

September 2020 - October 2020

Active member part of TAW (Tirana Architecture Weeks)

Management of social media/

Photographer/ Content Creator/ Support Team

VOLUNTEER STAFF

September 2019 - October 2019

Active member part of TDW (Tirana Design Week)

Management of social media/

Photographer/ Content Creator/ Support Team